When are you leaving?
Today.
Don't worry.
The matter is handled well.
You are running away.
And you say it's handled well?
Mind your own business.
I can just change my identity again.
This setup was too risky.
You should have been more careful.
Could it be riskier than what you did a year ago?
Am I wrong,
Emily?
We are being targeted by the police now,
and it's all thanks to you.
Don't forget,
your good sister,
Officer Zhuang Lan.
She's always been looking for Lighthouse.
It's getting late.
I'm leaving now.
Good luck.
Bye.
Good luck to you too.
Fang,
set up checkpoints at the bus station and the docks immediately.
She'll probably want to leave Mancheng as soon as possible.
We can't let her succeed.
Bai,
go visit her neighbors again,
as well as her colleagues.
She's very likely hiding in one of their homes.
We can't miss anything.
Understood.
Shao.
Go to her house for another trace identification,
to see if there are any new discoveries.
Understood.
Let's go.
It wasn't me.
Xiaobai asked me to give it to you.
Thank you.
Tell me,
when exactly did we leak the information
that let her escape early?
Remember I told you,
walls have ears in this world.
Fortunately,
the chief has agreed to issue an investigation notice for her.
She will be wanted across the city soon.
She won't escape this time.
I won't allow myself to fail again.
You won't.
Drink your coffee first.
Move.
What's in this bag?
Open it.
ID card.
Okay, next.
Anyway,
at least we have a definite target this time.
That is still some progress.
It's getting late.
Everyone, go back and rest.
Sis.
Let Captain Zhuang get some rest.
Sis,
we'll be leaving now.
Let's go.
Captain Zhuang, we'll head back now.
Accident.
It's the lighthouse's design.
There's no time.
They found me.
I can't leave.
Accidents or tomorrow,
which will come first?
Hello? Where are you?
I can't leave.
The train station is full of cops.
Arrange for me to leave now.
Right now, hurry!
Then wait for me at the cafe entrance now.
Okay.
In such a hurry to leave?
Let me see you off one last time.
Didn't you get off work?
Why are you back?
Sister.
As your subordinate,
I get off work when my boss says so.
But you are unhappy.
As your good sister,
I definitely have to accompany you.
Fine, you're sweet.
You, Shao.
What about you?
Finally got a clue.
After tonight,
there will be more variables tomorrow.
Besides,
I don't believe I can't catch her.
That's your style.
The young man is really energetic.
This comrade,
usually runs faster than anyone after work.
Why aren't you leaving this time?
Well,
if there's nothing to do,
who doesn't want to get off work early?
But I've never slacked off when there's work.
After all, I'm getting old.
I need less sleep.
What about you?
I'm waiting for you to take me home.
Mr. Cheng.
Amazing.
Brilliant.
Alright.
Since everyone wants to stay,
it seems we'll be working overtime tonight.
I'll treat you to late-night snacks.
I'll go.
You actually know how to treat people?
I can.
This kid runs so fast.
Almost as fast as I did when I was young.
Hello?
It's me.
Is everything all right?
You found Liu Ying?
That's great.
Where is she?
What?
Dead?
Mr. Shao,
you head to the scene first.
We'll be right there.
Notify Mia and Awang.
Okay.
Where is Mr. Cheng?
Oh right.
Forgot about him.
Forget it, let's not wait.
Let's go.
Go.
Shao.
Liu Ying.
How is it?
The massive impact caused multiple fractures all over her body,
and she died from severe internal bleeding.
This is clearly murder.
We were just about to investigate her,
and she dies.
It means we're looking in the right direction.
We're right.
It means we hit a sore spot,
the core of the Lighthouse organization.
Right.
These people are acting out of desperation.
They even kill their own.
This is the only surveillance video from the scene.
After processing by the technical department,
it's already the clearest version.
We still can't see who it is.
Sis,
aren't you afraid you won't see me again?
I promise you.
I'll visit you when I have time, okay?
Xiaobai.
Go and check
the owner's information of this car.
Bring her to me.
Got it, Sister.
I'll go to the scene
to check all the surveillance footage around it
and see if we can
find the direction she fled.
Is this you?
Zhuang Qing.
Could I have made a mistake?
Shao just said Liu Ying died.
We were a step too late.
Your micro-expressions tell me
you've guessed the killer's identity.
Others couldn't tell who she was.
But I recognized immediately
that she was my sister.
But she was already dead.
I saw her die in front of me with my own eyes.
I have a question.
Is she your biological sister?
My father brought her back.
She is not my biological sister.
But we grew up together.
I always treated her like my biological sister.
I knew it.
If a dead person suddenly comes back,
there is only one possibility.
She is not the same person.
I know that place.
I'll take you there.
This is the last place Zhuang Qing visited before she died.
Accidents and tomorrow
will arrive at the same time.
It really is her.
Solving these tricks
and finding the truth behind the accidents
is the purpose of our department.
Ahead,
there are more difficulties waiting for us.
Accident Investigation Team, attention!
Here!
Move out.
Copy that.